What did you think of others when you were told that you have ADD or ADHD
What was the first thought?
-It was both a relief and "damn!"
Then you fall into their "you are a diagnosis child".
Did you tell people around, or did you hold it to yourself
In the beginning, I became worried about whether it would affect me in working life.
"Will people think I'm stupid"
Once you say it to someone, they can speak this way:
"ADD, ie the disability"
What "disability"
You get a stamp, but I just have a little difficulty with the concentration.
They say, "Why can't you sit still and don't blame your ADHD."
I needed someone sitting next to it and wrote down the steps I would take.
Did you feel any change when you had received your diagnosis
For me it has been as before.
I have not received anything positive from it more than I know for myself what I have.
What would you like your teachers to do
I need someone who understands me and who is genuine and trying to help
And not just say "you have ADHD".
Now we will talk myths and claims about ADD and ADHD.
There are some
As we were going to test with you now.
We run "fact pingis".
Clara comes in with ping pong rackets to you all.
You see that it says "true" and "false" on them.
Sorry.
-"You better explain!"
“You can't ...“ Decide.
"You can't get it later in life."
You change your mind.
-That was what I meant.
Can anyone explain?
-It's...
There is no age limit for when you can get it.
It's about your psyche.
It develops in your brain.
It can come with age.
-Add and adhd are born with.
It can trigger, so you end up in investigation when you are older
But ADD and ADHD you are born with.
Can anyone pick up ... I don't have the sources.
We can find out later.
Write the sources down here, so people can read.